Devin Lim

Seattle, WA · devin@devinl.im · (253) 343-7980 · github.com/davay · linkedin.com/in/devinlim

Product-focused Project Manager/Software Engineer with 3 years of experience leading development and design of large-scale Fraud Protection systems. Demonstrated ability to adapt to a wide range of technologies and situations. Seeking opportunities to create fun products and further diversify my skill set through Data Science.

EDUCATION

Seattle UniversitySeattle, WAMS in Data ScienceSeptember 2023 - PresentSeattle UniversitySeattle, WABS in Computer Science, cum laudeSeptember 2018 - June 2020

EXPERIENCE

Centific (Microsoft)Redmond, WASoftware Design EngineerJuly 2021 - October 2023

Fraud Protection Tools Team

- Led a team of over 10 onshore and offshore developers building Microsoft's Fraud Protection ecosystem on .NET and Azure
- Client-side: Served as both an Individual Contributor and a Technical Project Manager, key contributor in the design of new feature requirements and adherence to compliance standards, including GDPR
- Vendor-side: Served as a Delivery Manager, responsible for hiring, coaching, and risk management

MAQ Software (Microsoft)
Software Data Operations Engineer

Redmond, WA October 2020 - June 2021

Fraud Protection Tools Team

Same role and duties as above

AmazonSeattle, WAStudent Intern - Seattle UniversityOctober 2019 - June 2020

Amazon Care Team

- Built a WebRTC video call web-app with Node.js and Express
- Built a robust, automated AWS pipeline that collects and analyzes information from individual calls
- Built a regression model to quantify call quality based on WebRTC metrics, visualized on the Elastic Stack

Polyverse CorporationBellevue, WACompiler Engineer InternJuly 2019 - September 2019

Co-Inventor of U.S. Patent 10,733,303: Polymorphic Code Translation Systems And Methods

• Researched methods to provide 100% mitigation of deserialization attacks through JVM token scrambling, which aims to prevent RCE attacks such as Equifax breach

MG2 CorporationSeattle, WAIT Support Specialist InternJuly 2018 - September 2018

Maintained, prevented, and resolved issues within the overall IT system

SKILLS

Languages: Python, HTML/CSS, Javascript/Typescript, R, C#, Bash, SQL, KQL

Data Technologies: Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn, Seaborn

Software Technologies: .NET, Razor, Azure (incl. ARM + DevOps), Node.js, Elastic Stack, WebRTC, OpenTelemetry

UNIX: Daily use & tinkering of Linux systems for 6+ years

Experienced in using various UNIX tools and shell scripting for automated, efficient workflow

Cloud Platforms: Experienced with large-scale robust systems in Azure, AWS, and GCP

IT: Windows Enterprise, Active Directory, Cisco switches, ManageEngine, Barracuda Networks